A Finding Aid to the American Federation of Arts Records, 1895-1993 (bulk 1909-1969), in the Archives of American Art AAA.amerfeda
Archives of American Art
Leonid: 53-1, 53-12
Leonid (Berman): 57-10
Leper, S. Deiva Njoman: 58-42
Lepere, Auguste: 62-45
Lepine, Stanislas: 59-19, 63-20
Leplae, Agnes: 61-1
Lerner, Arthur: 55-5
Lerner, Bob: 57-16, 59-56
Lesecq, Henry: 51-9
Leslie, Alfred: 58-26, 60-9, 60-22
Leslie, Charles R.: 65-10
Lester, William: 57-23
Lesueur, Eustache: 55-24
Lettau, Edward: 57-16
Levee, John: 54-27, 56-15, 57-12, 58-5, 58-29, 60-14, 60-22, 63-7
Lever, Hayley: 64-3
Levi, Carlo: 58-40
Levi, Julian: 57-28, 58-44, 60-4, ME-73
Levie, John E.: 64-1
Levigne, H.: 54-16
Levine, Arthur: 51-1, 53-5
Levine, David: 57-10, 61-15, 64-3
Levine, Jack: 55-9, 58-40, 59-6, 59-31, 60-13, 62-28, 62-31, ME-23, ME-41, ME-47, ME-75
Levinson, Mon: 64-12
Levitan, Israel: 56-2
Levy, Byron L.: 57-ee
Levyne, Sidney A.: 57-ee
Lewandowski, Edmund: 53-12, 55-13, 58-44
Lewel, Harry: 55-14
Lewen, Si: 54-8, 55-5, 58-5, 58-26
Lewerenz, Margaret: 51-15
Lewis, Arne: 53-26
Lewis, Arthur Allen: ME-7
Lewis, Ethel Kudrna: 60-5
Lewis, Henry: 58-27
Lewis, J.O.: ME-29
Lewis, John Chapman: 58-26, 63-7
Lewis, John M.: 62-10
Lewis, Norman: 53-12, 55-21, 59-6
Lewis Ross: 57-3
Lewis, Thomas D.: 62-10
Lewis, William A.: 57-10
Lewis & Bliss, Robert & Anna Campbell: 59-12
Lewitin, Landes: 62-27
Lewy, Kurt: 61-1
Leydenfrost, Robert: 53-5
Leyendecker, J.C.: 57-17
Li, Hua: 56-27
Liberman, Alexander: 62-45, 65-1, 65-4, ME-59
Liberte, Jean: 53-12, 55-3, ME-73
Libhart, Myles: 60-12
Libon, C.: 58-36
Libpton, Seymour: 57-38
Lichtenstein, Roy: 62-41, 64-26, 65-11, NY-17
Lichty, George: 57-3
Liebermann, Max: 61-25
Liebes, Dorothy: 62-15, 64-23
Liebling, Jerome: 59-12
Lies, Jonas: 62-17
Lietzke, Luke & Rolland: 57-6, 64-23
Limbach, Russell T.: NE-96
Linck-Daepp, Margrit: 61-1
Lincoln, Richard Mather: 57-14, 60-5
Lindaas Arne Jon: 57-14
Lindblad, Grethe: 57-14
Lindell, Lage: 62-44
Lindenmuth, Tod: 64-30
Lindenum, Richard J.: 62-10
Linder, Jean: 64-25
Lindh, Francesca Mascitti: 57-14
Lindh, Richard: 57-14
Lindheim, Mary: 57-6
Lindley, Ward: 53-26
Lindner, Richard: 60-4, ME-59
Lindstrom, Carl: 57-ee
Lindtmayer, Daneil (the Younger): 64-9
Lingelbach, Johannes: MMA-54-3
Linn Smith Associates: 62-24
Linnell, John: 55-24
Linsenmaier, Dwalter: 56-24
Lionni, Leo: 59-56
Lipchitz, Jacques: 57-15, 58-16, 59-6, 59-31, 60-42, 61-2, 61-24, 62-8, 63-31, ME-32, NY-20
Lipman-Wulf, Peter: 56-2
Lippi, Filippino: 56-16, 57-18
Lippold, Richard: 55-12, 56-22
Lipton, Seymour: 58-16, 60-22, 62-16, 65-1
Lissandrino: 62-20
Littell, R.: 52-7
Little, John: 59-23
Littleton, Harvey K.: 57-6, 60-5
Litvack, Harvey: 55-20, 58-3
Liverani, Emmanuele: 58-9
Lizars, William H.: ME-29
Llorens, Eva: 58-39
Lloyd, Timothy: 62-10
Lloyd, Morgan, & McGinty Lloyd, W.B., & Milton: ME-19
Lmppe, Peter: 51-21
Lo Medico, Thomas: 53-20
Lobdell, Frank: 58-39, 61-29
Lobel, Paul: 57-6
Lobmeyr, J. & L.: 61-1
Lochner, Stephen: 56-16
Lockwood, George: 58-39
Loebl, Schlossman & Bennett: 65-3
Loerner, Henry: 53-1
Loew, Michael: 56-2, 58-26, 64-31
Loffredo, Silvio: 54-16
Loftus, John: 65-11
Logan, A.: 62-2
Loggie, Henlen A.: 53-1
Loire, Gabriel: 61-1
Lombard, Lambert: 55-24, 67-19
Longchamps, Gaston: 56-2
Longo, Vincent: 53-16, 53-26, 55-20, 56-25, 60-3, 60-22, 60-24, 64-7, 65-11
Loomis, Dana A.: 65-11
Lopez, Carlos: 53-5
Loran, Erle: 58-7, 61-26
Lorca, F. Garcia: 58-36
Lorch, Melchior: 55-10
Lotiron, Robert: NE-96
Lotteman, Hal: 55-2, 55-5
Lotzgesell, Gloria: 53-17
Loubchansky, Marcelle: 64-10
Loughney, Hermine: 56-2
Love, Joseph P.: ME-75
Love, Kermet: 59-19
Lovell, Rosa Lee: 65-7
Lovera, James: 60-5
Low, David: 57-3
Low, Joseph: 54-17, 61-33
Lowen, Si: 60-1
Lowengrund, Margaret: 53-2, 53-5, 53-16, 54-18, NE-96
Lozano, Matias: 64-23
Lozowick, Louis: 56-26, ME-7
Lsteiner, Velma Lee: 58-3
Lubroth, Mil: 62-3
Lucas, Eugenio: 55-19
Lucchesi, Bruno: 59-12
Lucebert, L.G. Swanswijk: 60-15, 61-4
Lucioni, Luigi: ME-73
Ludins, Eugene: 58-5
Lueders, Jim C.: 55-14
Luginbuhl, Ursel: 61-1
Luisa, Maria: 60-17
Lukin, Sven: 65-4
Lukosius, Richard: 56-27
Luks, George Benjamin: 55-19, 57-11, 58-34, 59-6, 62-17, 62-30, ME-41, NY-19
Luksus, Tzaims: 64-23
Lund, David: NY-10
Lundin, Ingeborg: 56-3
Lundquist, Evert: 62-44
Lundy, Victor A.: 64-11
Lurcat, Jean: 53-2, 61-1
Luster Guy: 60-43
Lutyens, Edwin (Sir): 61-22
Lutz, Ann Winefred: 65-6
Lutz, Dan: 56-19
Lux, Gwen: 52-4, 53-20, 59-25
Lyberis, William: 53-26
Lynes, George Platt: 58-20
Lyon, Jane S.: 65-11
Lyons, Nathan: 60-12, 61-13
M.E. Haefeli, Hubacher & Steiger: 53-21
M.H. Birge & Company: NY-14
Maas, Bernard: 62-10
Maas, Marcolino (Reverend): 53-25
Mabe, Manabu: 60-17
Macchiarini, Peter: 51-15
Maccoy, Guy: 58-3
Macdonald, Jerry: 60-5
MacDonald, Pirie: 56-5
Macdonald-Wright, Stanton: 55-15, 57-10, 58-34, 60-27
Machlin, Sheldon: 63-29
MacIver,Loren: 55-9, 57-2, 57-11, 59-10, 59-24, 62-28, 64-30, 65-11, ME-7, ME-41, ME-73
Mackay, Marion: 53-17
Macke, August: 56-7
MacKenzie, Alex & Warren: 59-12
MacKenzie, Frederick: 62-12
Mackie & Kamrath: ME-19
MacKnight, Dodge: 63-1, 64-30
MacPherson Robert: 62-25, NY-1
Maddox, Jerold: 53-26, 63-24
Madhloom, Tarir: 56-29
Madley, Elizabeth: 55-22
Madson, Jack: 57-12
Maeda, Chikuhosai: 65-12
Mafai, Mario: 58-23
Magafan, Ethel: 53-12, 55-5, 58-3, ME-73
Magalhaes, Aloisio: 58-15
Magnasco, Alessandro: 65-10, 67-19
Magnelli, Alberto: 58-23
Magritte, Rene: 60-4, 61-4, 64-4
Maguire, T.H.: ME-29
Mahl, Claire: 56-2
Maillet, Leo: 53-2
Maillol, Aristide: 61-9, 62-5, ME-32
Maini, Marino: 54-27
Mair, William: 58-12
Maitin, Samuel: 62-3
Majdrakoff, Ivan: 53-24, 61-25
Majors, William: 66-9
Makovkin, Sasha: 58-32
Malagodi, Gaetano: 58-9
Maldarelli, Oronzio: 52-4, 55-12. 56-2, 56-22
Males, Miha: 56-15, 56-21
Malicoat, Philip C.: 64-29, 64-30
Malkin, Robert: 62-33
Mallary, Robert: 62-41, 63-12, 63-29, 64-20, 64-25, ME-55
Maloney, Daniel: 64-3
Maloof, Sam: 55-22
Mame, Maison: 61-1
Manabe, Mitsuo: 65-12
Manbeck, Dorathee G.: 60-5
Manchek, Albert: 56-2
Mandel, Howard: 53-5
Manes, Nancy C.: 57-14, 58-32
Manessier, Alfred: 54-18, 56-15, 58-15, 60-14, 60-15, 64-2, 64-10, NE-96
Manet, Edouard: 57-18, 67-19, MMA-54-2
Manetta, Edward: ME-75
Mangravite, Peppino: 56-2, 60-1, 65-11
Mann Samuel: 58-32, 64-23
Manners Leroy: 53-26
Manship, Paul: 59-25
Manso, Leo: 58-26, 61-15, 64-29, 64-30, ME-73
Manville, Elsie: 64-3
Manzu, Giacomo: 55-7, 57-34, 58-35, 58-40, 60-42, 63-31
Manzu & Morandi: 58-18
Manzur, David: 63-7
Marantz, Irving: 56-13, 64-30
Maratti, Carlo: 55-24, 62-36, 64-6
Marc, Franz: 56-7, 59-36, 62-29
Marca-Relli, Corrado di: 56-12, 64-2, 64-20, 65-4, ME-33, ME-42, ME-73
Marcecak, Edward: 58-39
Marcel Breuer & Assoc: 64-11, 65-9
March Charles E.: 62-10
Marchand, Andre: 59-5
Marchionni, Carolo: 59-40
Marchutz, Leo: NE-96
Marcks, Gerhard: 54-16, 56-7, 58-35, 59-36, 61-4, 61-9
Marcoussis, Louis: 59-5, 60-14
Marcus, Edwin: 57-3
Marcus, Marcia: 62-30, 64-26, 65-2, NY-10, NY-17, NY-18
Marechal: 59-40
Marein, Shirley: ME-75
Marfaing, Andre: 64-2
Marggraf, Zella: 55-22
Margo, Boris: 51-6, 53-2, 53-16, 55-3, 55-9, 56-1, 56-2, 56-25, 56-26, 57-1, 57-32, 57-36, 58-3, 58-43, 59-10, 60-3, 60-24, 61-7, 62-38, 63-7, 64-7, 64-29, 64-30, ME-7, ME-59, ME-73, NY-3
Margoulies, Berta: 52-4
Marguerite: 56-2
Margules, deHirsh: 56-2
Margulies, Joseph: 64-30
Mariani, Vincint: 58-39
Marie-Rose, Henri: 58-7
Marieschi, Michele: 64-6
Maril, Herman: 56-13, 61-7, 64-30
Marin, John: 53-6, 54-25, 55-15, 55-16, 58-34, 58-42, 58-43, 59-31, 60-13, 61-25, 62-16, 62-28, 64-31, ME-7, ME-23, ME-26, ME-27, ME-31, ME-32, ME-41, NY-5, NY-7&7b, NY-20
Marini, Aida: 56-29
Marini, Marino: 53-1, 54-18, 57-34, 58-15, 59-5, 61-4, 63-31, 64-2, NE-96
Marisol: 62-41, 63-30
Mark, J.W.: 62-2
Markell, Jack: 58-6
Markey, Barbara R.: 58-16, 58-32, 58-35
Markman Ronald: 61-15
Marks, Cynthia: 64-7
Marot, Daniel: 59-40
Marsh, Reginald: 53-5, 54-25, 55-16, 57-9, 57-22, 60-13, 60-27, 62-17, 62-28, 62-30, ME-7, ME-31, NY-5
Marshall, Helen: 55-19
Marsicano, Nicholas: 60-22, 60-43, 61-15
Martens, Michel: 61-1, ME-29
Martha Crawford Associates: 61-30
Marthas, Takis: 61-4
Martin, Agnes: 60-41, 64-26
Martin, Andre: 60-25
Martin, David Stone: 56-24
Martin, Fletcher: 55-19, 56-2, 59-6
Martin, Fred: 65-11
Martin, Homer Dodge: 59-6, 60-28, ME-11, NY-4
Martin, Joe: 63-5
Martin, John: 62-12, 65-10
Martin, Keith: 55-2, 55-6, 56-19, 59-10
Martin, Kenneth: 61-21
Martin, Knox: 56-2
Martin, Mary: 61-21
Martin, Philip: 57-27
Martin, Roger: 56-27
Martin, Stefan: 64-7
Martin, Vincente: 60-17
Martin, W.B.: 56-25
Martin, Walt: 61-35
Martinelli, Ezio: 56-12, 57-15, 60-4, 60-22, 62-3, 65-11
Martinez, Raul: 56-28
Martinez-Pedro, Luis: 56-28, 62-6
Martino, Antonio P.: 55-2
Martz, Gordon & Jane: 64-23
Marville, Charles: NY-1
Marx, Robert E.: 53-16, 55-20, 64-7
Mary, Josefa (Sister): 62-10
Maryan: 64-25, NY-18
Masaccio: 57-18
Masanobu, Okumura: 58-17
Mascarin, Mario: 61-1
Mascherini, Marcello: 55-7
Maselli, Titina: 55-19, 57-27
Masereel, Frans: 54-16, 57-21
Mason, Alice Trumbell: 53-5, 53-16, 55-3, 56-2, 56-26, 57-32, 57-36, 60-24, 60-41, 62-8
Mason, Emily: 55-20
Mason, Mike: 58-3
Massari, Lucio: 59-40
Massin, Eugene: 57-35
Masson, Andre: 60-14, 61-9, 62-8, NE-96
Masso,n Emile: 64-1
Masson, John J.: 62-10
Massys, Cornelis: 56-16
Master, C.B.: 55-10
Master, M.Z.: 55-10
Mastroianni, Umberto: 61-4
Masurovsky, Gregory: 60-12, 61-4
Mata, Roberto: 60-17
Matare, Ewald: 56-7, 59-36
Mategot Mathieu: 61-1
Matham, Jacob: 63-9
Mathewson, Milton P.: 57-ee
Mathieu, Georges: 57-27
Mathisson, M.J.: 53-26
Matinez, Ricardo: 63-24
Matisse, Henri: 57-18, 57-30, 59-5, 60-14, 60-24, 61-9, 63-14, 63-17, ME-40
Matranga, Frank: 62-10
Matsui: 63-21
Matsumoto, Hozan: 63-21, NY-21
Matta, Echaurren Roberto Sebastián: 51-4, 55-13, 57-9, 59-31, 60-4, 60-14, 61-4, 62-8, 62-29
Matte, Jean Rene: 53-17
Matter, Herbert: VA-54-1
Mattern, Karl: 53-1
Matteson, Tompkins Harrison: 58-27
Matthew, B. Brady Studio: 64-28
Matthews, John: 58-32
Matthews, Wanda: 58-3
Matthiasdottir Louisa: NY-18
Mattioli, Lodovico: 64-6
Mattson, Henry: 53-12, 57-11
Matzdorf, Kurt J.: 61-17, ME-75
Mauldin, Bill: 57-3
Maurand, C.: 54-12
Maurer, Alfred Henry: 54-10, 54-25, 55-15, 60-13, 60-27, 61-25, ME-31
Maurer, Leonard: 55-2, 55-8, 61-7
Maurer, Louis: 59-6
Maute, Paul: 62-15
Mauve, Anton: MMA-54-4
Mawzey, Merrit: ME-7
Maximowna, Ita: 53-15
Maxwell, Paul: 54-27
Maxwell, Robert: 65-6
May, Dave: 62-31
May, John: 57-6
May, John & Susan: 64-23
May, Ruth: 62-33
Mayer, Deanna: 62-10
Mayhew, Nathaniel: 62-2
Mayhew, Richard: NY-10
Maynard, Florence & Karl: 64-28
Mayr: 63-19
Maziarz, John: 56-27
Mazur, Michael: 60-3, 64-7, 65-11
Mazur, Richard Andrew: 57-14, 58-32
Mazzone, Michael: 56-27
Mazzuola, Francesco: 64-6
McAdams, Alfred H.: 55-2
McAvoy, Thomas D.: 58-A&B
McBey, James: 62-12, 64-3
McCarroll, William J.: 62-10
McCarter, Henry: 63-3
McCarthy, Francis Joseph: SD-8
McCary, Winsor: 57-3
McClellan, Douglas: 55-6
McClellan, John: 54-18
McClintock, Byron: 54-18
McCombe, Leonard: 58-A&B, 59-56, L-7
McConnell, James: 60-3
McCoy, John W.: 53-1, 53-8, 63-3
McCray, Dorothy: 60-3
McCray, James: 58-7
McCullough, Joseph: 55-2, 58-39
McCutcheon, John T.: 57-3
McDade, Gwen D.: 59-27
McDermott, Mary Ellen: 58-16, 58-35
McDonald, Gene: 64-23
McFadden, Elizabeth: 58-26, 59-1
McGarrell, James: 55-20, 56-26, 60-12, 63-12, 64-20, ME-73, NY-3, NY-18
McGary, Donna: 60-5
McGee, Eldon F.: 53-17
McGee, Joyce Barnett: 60-5
McGee, William: 62-41
McGinnis, Christine: 64-7
McGlauchlin, Patricia: 62-10
McIlvaine, William: 64-1
McIntosh, Harrison: 57-6
McIntyre, Jeanne: 62-15
McIntyre, Keith: 57-23
McIntyre, William R.: 58-7
McKain, Bruce: 62-38, 64-29, 64-30
McKay, Arthur F.: 58-6, 59-3
McKeeby, Byron: 64-7
McKibben, Teal: 59-12
McKie, Roy: 55-13
McKim, William W.: 65-7
McKinley, Donald L.: 60-5
McKinley, Ruth Gowdy: 57-6, 57-14, 58-32
McKinnell, Nan: 60-5
McKinnell, Jr., James F.: 60-5
McKnee, John: 56-2
McKnight, Elaine: 60-3
McLaughlin, Coille: 62-10
McLaughlin, Gerald W.: 56-12, 58-5, 62-1
McLaughlin, John: 58-7, 60-41, 63-12
McLean, William: 58-7
McManus, George: 57-3
McMath, George A.: 64-21
McMillan, Constance: 57-31
McMillin, Tom: 64-23
McMurtrie, William Birch: 64-1
McNeil, George: 55-2, 58-5, 62-38, ME-55, ME-73
McRae, John: ME-29
McSherry, Naida: 62-10
McVey, William: 59-25
McVicker, J. Jay: 58-3
McViker, Julia: 52-7
Mead, Roderick: 58-3, 62-8
Meadows, Bernard: 61-4, 63-31
Meany, Philip: 56-25
Mecikalski, Eugene: 53-16, 56-25
Medellin, Jesse: 57-23
Meehan, Thomas: 55-19
Meeker, Dean: 53-16, 55-20, 56-25, 57-12, 58-3, 58-6, 59-10, 62-3, 64-7
Meeker, J.R.: ME-11
Meeks, Martha F.: 62-10
Meert, Joseph: 56-2, 56-13, 58-16
Meguro, Junzaburo: 65-12
Meierhans, Joe: 56-2
Meigs, Mary: 64-30
Meigs, Walter: 53-14, 59-1, ME-73
Meijer, Mans: 61-20
Meirowsky, Katja: NE-48
Meistermann, Georg: 54-18, 56-7, 59-36
Meistermann, Greg: 53-11
Melcarth, Edward: 57-2, 58-40
Melchers, Gari: 63-1
Meli, Salvatore: 61-1
Melli, Robert: 58-23
Mellon, James: ME-75
Meltzoff, Stanley: 56-24
Memling, Hans: 56-16
Memoun, S.: 58-36
Mendez, Louis: 57-14
Menkes, Sigmund: 53-5, 59-31, ME-73
Menkes, Zygmunt: 55-3, 57-11
Menzel, Adolph Friedrich: 62-20
Menzio, Francesco: 58-23
Mercati, Giovanni Battista: 64-6
Mercher, Henri: 61-1
Merian, Matthieu: 64-19, ME-65
Merida, Carlos: 62-6
Merrill, Claude M.: 62-10
Mertz, Franz: 53-15
Meryon, Charles: 62-18
Mesibov, Hugh: 56-2
Messersmith, Fred: 65-11
Messina, Joseph: 58-16
Metal, Martin: 51-9, 51-15
Metcalf, James: 65-1
Metcalf, Willard Leroy: 57-11, 63-1, NY-16
Metsovaara-Nystrom, Marjatta: 62-15
Metzinger, Jean: 57-9, 57-30, 62-29, ME-32
Meunier, Constantin: 62-45
Meydum, Floris: 61-1
Meyer, Bob: 62-15
Meyer, Charles E.: 57-14
Meyer, Howard: ME-19
Meyer, J.: 58-36
Meyerowitz, William: ME-7
Meyers, Ben: 56-2
Michael, Saphier Associates, Inc.: 61-30
Michaux, Henri: 61-4, 61-11
Michel, Geoges: 55-24, 63-20
Michelangelo: 57-18
Michelsson, Brigit: 57-14
Michnick, Davis: 52-4
Middelboe, Rolf: 62-15
Middeleer, Charles: 62-33
Middleman, Raoul: ME-75
Middleton, Sam: NY-10
Midener, Peggy: 53-24, ME-75
Mielatz, Charles F. W.: 64-3
Mielziner, Jo: 63-19, 4-35, 62-14
Mihelic, France: 54-18, 56-21
Miki, Jun: 58-A&B
Milan, Raul: 56-28
Milbrath, Harold A.: 57-6
Mildwoff, Steven: 64-23
Miles, Jeanne: 60-41
Mili, Gjon: 59-56
Millan, Edward: 53-12
Millares, Manolo: 61-4, 61-29
Miller, Alfred Jacob: 59-34, 61-3, 64-1, ME-11
Miller, Alice: 58-39
Miller, Barse: 53-8
Miller, Francis: 58-A&B
Miller, Frederick A.: 57-6
Miller, Herald G.: 52-11
Miller, Herman: ME-4
Miller, John B.: 54-8, 63-5
Miller, John Paul: 54-43
Miller, Kenneth Hayes: 55-16, 62-30
Miller, Lea Van P.: 57-6, 62-15
Miller, Martha: 60-5, 61-17, ME-75
Miller, Richard E.: 64-30, NY-16
Miller, William Rickarby: 56-18, 59-34, 64-3
Miller, Jr., Daniel: 58-39
Millet, Jean F.: 63-20
Millet, Jean Francois: MMA-54-2
Millet, Kate: 65-6
Milliken, Gibbs: NY-17
Millman, Edward: 55-13, 58-44
Mills, Joan Studley: 53-17
Mills, Jody: 53-24
Milono, Germano: 64-11
Milton, Peter W.: 64-7
Minagawa, Taizo: 65-12
Minaux, André: 54-18, 58-15
Minewski, Alex: 55-5
Minguzzi, Luciano: 55-7, 60-15, 62-40, 63-31, ME-56
Minoru Yamasaki & Assoc: 62-24, 65-3
Mirko: 59-35
Mirko (Basaldella): 54-27
Miró, Joan: 56-15, 60-4, 60-14, 60-15, 61-9, 62-8, 62-18, 62-41, ME-55, NE-96
Mishilani, James: 56-29
Mistein, Emanuel: 61-17
Mitcham, Fred: 57-23, 57-ee
Mitchell, Bruce: 53-5
Mitchell, Dow P.: 55-20
Mitchell, Fred: 58-39
Mitchell, James A.: 61-31
Mitchell, Jill: 53-24
Mitchell, Joan: 60-9, 60-22, ME-55, NY-10
Mitchell, Mary: 53-24
Mitchell & Giurgola Associates: 62-24
Mitchell & Ritchey: 65-3
Mitsui, Asoo: 65-12
Mitsuoki, Tosa: 63-14
Mitzman, Barney: 55-20
Miura, Kageo: 65-12
Miyamoto: 63-21
Miyasaki, George: 58-3, 58-7, 60-24, ME-73, NY-3
Mizuno, Sokaku: 65-12
Mock, Rudolf: 53-21
Model, Hanns: 61-1
Model, Lisette: 56-5
Modersohn-Becker, Paula: 56-7
Modigliani, Amedo: 57-18, 57-34, 60-14, NY-7&7b
Moffett, George: 58-20
Moffett, Ross: 64-29, 64-30
Mogelof, Simon: 57-ee
Moholy-Nagy, László: 51-9, 58-43, 62-29, 64-10
Mola, Pier Francesco: 62-36
Moldovan, Kurt: 56-15
Mole, J.H.: 62-12
Moller, Hans: 53-5, 53-25, 55-3, 55-8, 55-9, 56-2, 57-1, 57-10, 58-16, 58-26, 59-1, 61-7, 62-6, 64-31, ME-26, ME-73
Molly, Coman Wallpapers: NY-14
Mommer, Paul: 55-3
Mondo, Domenico: 59-40
Mondrian, Piet: 57-18, 58-43, 64-19, ME-65
Monet, Claude: 57-18, 60-14, 61-10, MMA-54-4, NY-7&7b
Monner, Al: 57-16
Monogrammist, H.W.G.: 55-10
Monroe, Keith: 58-16
Montagna, Benedetto: 57-37
Montalon, Mademoiselle: 59-40
Montenegro, Enrique: 55-6
Monticelli, A.: 63-20
Monticelli, Marco Tullio: 61-1
Monza, Louis: 56-2
Moody, John Robert: 53-17
Moore, Charles H.: NY-4
Moore, Charles W.: 64-11, 64-21
Moore, David: 56-2
Moore, Fay Mowery: 64-30
Moore, Henry: 53-1, 54-27, 58-15, 60-14, 60-42, 61-4, 62-40, 63-31, ME-55, ME-56, NE-96
Moore, Jack D.: 56-26
Moore, Werton Dee: 57-ee
Moore, Winchell M.: 58-32
Morales, Amaral y: 59-27
Moran, Edward: 63-15
Moran, Thomas: 59-34, 59-40, 61-3, 64-1, 65-10, ME-11, ME-32
Morandi, Giorgio: 57-34, 58-23, 61-4
Moras, Ferdinand: 64-1
Morath, Inge: 60-25
Morato: 61-1
Moreau, Louis Gabriel: 63-17
Moreau (the Younger), Marcantonio: NY-9
Morehouse, William: 54-27, 60-1
Moreland, William L.: 54-8, 61-35
Morelli, Enzo: 51-18
Moreni, Mattia: 58-23, 61-11, 61-16
Moreno, Servando Cabrera: 56-28
Moretti, Alberto: 56-15
Morgan, Alan E.: 64-11
Morgan, Andrew W.: 65-7
Morgan, Frances Mallory: 52-4
Morgan, Matt: 57-17
Morgan, Maud: 59-24
Morgan, Norma: 56-21, 59-12, 62-3, 64-7, 66-9
Morgan, Randall: 55-8, 55-9
Morgan, William: 58-27
Morino, Kako: 65-12
Morisot, Berthe: 62-45
Morita: 63-21
Morland, George: 65-10
Morlotti, Ennio: 58-23
Mormanno: 62-20
Morozewski, Stefan: 56-25
Morris, Carl: 53-5, 56-1, 58-7, 58-42, 59-45, 64-7, 65-11, ME-73
Morris George L.K.: 53-5, 53-9, 55-3, 55-9, 55-11, 56-2, 57-28, 58-26, 58-44, 59-10, 59-23
Morris, Hilda: 57-12, 58-7, 60-4, 63-12, 64-7
Morris, Kyle: 57-10, 59-10, 61-29, 63-7, ME-33, ME-42
Morris, William: 63-5
Morris, Ostego Company: NY-15
Morrison, Fritzi: 53-1
Morrison, George: 53-12, 56-1, 64-29, 64-30
Morrison, Mark: 52-4, 53-20
Morrow, S.J.: 54-12
Morse: 54-25, 57-17
Morse, Ralph: 58-A&B
Morse, Samuel F.B.: 60-13, 62-17, ME-11, ME-31
Mortenson, Richard: 61-4
Mortimer, J.: 62-12
Mosca, August: 64-3
Mose, Eric: 56-24
Moseid, Torvald: 57-40
Moser, Karl: 53-21
Moses, Anna M. Robertson: 55-19
Moses, Edward: 62-41
Moskowitz, Robert: 62-41
Motherwell, Robert: 54-10, 58-26, 59-6, 59-23, 64-30, ME-7, ME-33, ME-42, ME-73
Moti, Kaiko: 56-21
Motyka, Edmund: 61-30
Moukheibir, Aida: 56-29
Moule, Marian: 55-22
Moulthrop, Reuban: 62-2
Mount, William Sidney: 54-25, 58-27, 59-6, 59-24, 59-34, 60-13, 60-28, 62-17, 64-1, 65-2, ME-11, ME-31, ME-41
Mount Wilson & Polomar Observatories: 59-56
Mourlot: 59-5
Moy, Seong: 53-2, 53-16, 55-3, 55-20, 56-2, 56-15, 56-25, 56-26, 57-32, 58-42, 59-1, 60-22, 60-24, 62-3, 62-8, 64-7, 64-29, 64-30, ME-73, NY-3
Moyer, Frances: 65-6
Moyer, Roy: 61-15
Mruch, Walter: 58-5
Muccini, Marcello: 58-40
Mueller, George: 55-6, 56-2, ME-33, ME-42, ME-73
Mueller, Otto: 56-7, 59-36
Mueller, Riette: 53-16
Mueller, Robert Emmett: 56-25
Muench, John: 54-18, 60-3
Muir, William H.: 64-31
Mulier, Pieter (the Younger): 62-36
Muller, Jan: 58-12, 60-43
Muller, Jean: NY-18
Muller, Robert: 60-14, 60-42
Muller-Hermann, Irma: 61-1
Mullican, Lee: 60-4, 60-22
Munakata, Shiko: 60-15, 61-4
Munch, Edvard: 62-5, 62-28, ME-55
Mundal, Maria: ME-75
Mundy, Henry: 61-4, 64-2
Munkedal, Grethe: 57-14
Munn, Paul Sanby: 62-12
Munnings, Alfred (Sir): 55-19
Munoz, Hilario: 64-25
Munzner, Aribert: 65-7
Murakami: 63-21
Murch, Walter: 53-25, 55-13, 56-24, 58-5, 60-1, 60-4, 61-7, 62-1, 62-16, 64-4, 64-19, 65-11, ME-59, ME-65, ME-73
Muro, J. Antono Fernandez: 60-17
Murphy, Frank: 58-20
Murpy, John Francis: 57-16, 63-15, 64-3, 65-10
Murray, Judith A.: 62-3
Murray-Jones-Murray: 64-11
Murtic, Edo: 59-16
Music, Antonio: 53-2, 55-7, 56-15, 57-34, 58-23, 60-14, 61-11
Mussett, Charles: 56-9
Muybridge, Eadweard
Mydans, Carl: 58-A&B
Myers, Jerome: 57-2, 62-30, 64-3
Myers Joel: 62-10, 64-23
Myers, Malcolm H.: 58-6, 60-3, 62-3
Myers, Virginia A.: 55-20
Myrer, Angele: 58-3
Nadar, Paul: 56-5
Nadelman, Elie: 61-25, 63-31, ME-55
Nae-hyon, Pak: 58-33
Naef, Hannibal: 53-21
Nagare, Masayuki: 63-23
Nagel: ME-29
Nagle, Ron A.: 62-10
Nagler, Fred: 58-16, 63-33
Nahl, Charles: ME-29
Nahl, Johann August (the Elder): 59-40
Nail, Reilly: 53-1
Naiveu, Matthys: MMA-54-3
Najarian, Hovak: 60-5
Naka, Seitaro: 65-12
Nakajima, Michiko: 65-12
Nakamura, Kazuo: 59-3
Nakamura, Koya: 65-12
Nakano: 63-21
Nakashima, George: 64-23
Nakazato, Shigetoshi: 65-12
Nakazato, Tadao: 65-12
Nakian, Reuben: 63-31
Naldini, Giovanni Battista: 62-20
Nama, George A.: 64-7
Namuth, Hans: 58-20, 62-45
Nancy McClelland, Inc: NY-14
Nanteuil, Robert: NY-9
Napoli, Giuseppe: 56-2
Naramore, Bain, Brady & Johanson: 65-3
Narducci, Pietro: 58-9
Nash, Paul: 62-12
Nashimit, S.: 58-36
Nason, Thomas Willoughby: ME-7
Nast, Thomas: 57-3, 59-6
Natali, Giuseppe: 61-22
Natinguerra, A. Bartoli: 51-18
Natkin, Robert: 62-37, 64-2, ME-60
Natoire, Charles-Joseph: 55-24
Nattier, Jean Marc: 62-36
Natzler, Gertrude & Otto: 51-15, 55-22, 57-6
Naum, Gheorghe: 56-21
Nay, Ernst Wilhelm: 54-18, 56-7, 59-36
Nay, Mary Spencer: 56-25
Neagle, John: 58-14, 63-3, ME-11, ME-32
Neal, Quintin: 57-6
Neal, Reginald H.: 53-5, 58-15, 60-3, 60-22
Nebbia, Thomas: 63-2
Neel, Alice: 64-26
Neer, Eglon Hendrik van der: 54-11, MMA-54-3
Neeterby, Elena: 51-15
Negoro, Minnie: 57-6
Negret, Edgar: 63-29
Neili, Armin (Dr.): 53-21
Nelson, Carl: 64-31
Nelson, George: 53-17, 64-21
Nelson, Helen: 58-16
Nelson, Robert: 54-8
Nemeny, George: 64-21
Nepote, Alexander: 53-5, 58-7
Neroni: 63-19
Nervi, Pier Luigi: 59-29
Nesch, Rolf: 56-7
Neter-Kahler, Greten: 61-1
Netscher, Casper: MMA-54-3
Neuhart, Marilyn: 65-6
Neuhaus, & Taylor: 65-3
Neustadt, Barbara: 58-3, 58-35, 60-24
Neutra, Richard J.: 59-15
Nevelson, Louise: 53-20, 56-2, 59-14, 60-22, 60-24, 62-8, 62-40, 63-29, 64-19, 65-1, ME-56, ME-65
Newal, Reginald H.: 56-25
Newkirk, Paul J.: 56-27
Newman, Arnold: 58-20, 63-8
Newman, Barnett: ME-59
Newman, Robert Loftin: 59-6, 59-34, ME-11
Newswanger, Christian: 53-12
Newton, Algernon: 62-12
Newton, William: 61-22
Ng Win: 62-31
Nichols, Perry: 57-23
Nichols, Jack: 56-21, 59-3
Nichols, Marie: 62-15
Nicholson, Ben: 56-21, 57-9, 59-31, 60-14, 61-4, 61-9, ME-32, ME-40
Nicholson, Francis: 62-12
Nickford, Juan: 56-12, 58-16
Nicoidski, Robert: 61-23
Nicolas, Joep: 53-25
Niederer, Roberto: 61-1
Nielssen, Finn: 57-40
Niemeyer, Oscar: 64-11
Niepoort, Paul: 53-24
Niese, Henry: 55-2, 57-12, NY-10
Niewald, Wilbur: 58-39, 65-7
Nigro, Joanne: 53-26
Nilson, Johann Esias: 59-40
Nilson, Marianne: 57-14
Nims, Rufus: 64-21
Nims & Browne: 58-1
Nisbel, Nils: 57-14
Nisbet, Robert H.: 64-3
Nishikawa: 63-21
Nison, Jean: 58-16
Nivola, Constantino: 55-6, 55-13, 64-20, 56-2, 59-28, 62-16, 65-3
No-su, Pak: 58-33
Noack, A.: 64-28
Noble, John A.: 56-25, 64-30
Noble, Joseph V.: 62-45
Noel, Georges: 64-2
Noel, Leon: ME-29
Noguchi, Isamu: 59-6, 62-40, ME-56
Noland, Kenneth: ME-73
Nolde, Emil: 56-7, 59-36, 60-14, 62-27
Noma, Yoshiko: 62-8
Nome, Sigured: 57-40
Nooms, Reinier (Zeeman): 60-40
Noordhoek, Wim: 51-3, 53-2
Nordfeldt, B.J.O.: 53-12, 57-30, 61-25, 64-29, 64-30
Nordgreeu, Erik: 52-5
Norman, Dorothy: 56-5
Norris: 64-5
Norwood, Richard: 54-42
Nosaka, Koki: 65-12
Noteriani, Philip: 58-16
Novelli, Gastone: 60-20, 62-41
November, David: 62-10
Novick, Jennie: ME-75
Noyes, Eliot: 62-34
Nunes, Gordon: 53-5
Nurkse, Harriet Berger: 56-25
Nydal, Gabriella: 57-14
Nygaard, Axel: 52-5
Nyman, Olle: 62-44
Nzgaard, Lisbeth A.: 53-24
O'Connell, George: 64-7
O'Connell, Michael: 62-15
O'Connor, Thom: 64-7
O'Hara, Bernhard: 56-2
O'Hara, Eliot: 53-1, 53-8
O'Hara, Frederick: 60-15
O'Keeffe, Georgia: 54-25, 55-11, 55-15, 59-6, 59-31, 60-13, 60-27, 63-14, ME-7, ME-23, ME-31, ME-41
O'Neil, John: 55-6
O'Neill, Desmond: 55-2
O'Neill, Michael T.: 65-11
O'Neill, Rose: 57-3
O'Sullivan, Timothy H.: 54-12, 62-25, NY-1
O'Stock: 53-21
Ober, Hermann: 53-11, 60-15